It's Friday! Enjoy Simple English 森崎ウィンです
毎週金曜日は怪盗紳士ルパンの名作をお届けします
今月はシャーロックホームズ arrives too late 遅すぎたシャーロックホームズ
そうこの話シャーロックホームズが登場いたします
画家ベルモンになりすまし
キベルメニル城に潜り込んだルパン
しかし上司のドゥバンヌに
ルパンではないかと疑われています
どんな展開になるのでしょうか
それではレッツダイブインドゥストーリー
Mr.Vilmont
You really look like our Saint Lupin
If my cousin had not introduced you to me
and if I did not like your paintings of the sea
I would have called the police immediately
The dinner guests at Tiber Menil Castle laughed
The owner of the castle, Devon, was making fun of the painter, Vellemont
as he took them on a tour around the castle
You are running out of time
Tonight is your last chance
Vellemont decided to take part in the joke
What do you mean?
the great english detective sherlock holmes will come here tomorrow afternoon at four o'clock
i asked him to come because i know lupin and his men are near here
they have robbed nearby castles i am probably next
all the guests were surprised to hear this
then devon pointed to a bookcase
there was a small empty space between two big books
この宇宙の歴史について、この2本の本について書いた本がありました。
この本には、外側にあるこの宇宙に移る秘密のマップが含まれていました。
そして、この本は1ヶ月前に消失しました。
悪いことを聞いているのですが、
シャーロック・ホームズに助けた理由は何でしょうか?
それは唯一の理由ではありません。
この宇宙については、パリの国際博物館にある他の本もあります。
That book also disappeared.
With these two books, you can know exactly how to get in and out of this castle.
I see. It sounds serious.
Do you know where the entrance is and where it leads to?
That is the problem.
We keep many precious treasures in this room.
And I know the tunnel leads to the room we are in.
But that is all I know.
One of the guests was a priest.
このキャステルについては、彼は言いました。
ディヴァンさん、ここにある証拠があります。
覚えておいてください。2つのフランスの王様がプズルに逃げられました。
教祖によって、ヘンリー4人とルイ16人はこのキャステルに留まりました。
彼らはこの秘密のトンネルを使っていたと言われていました。
そして、彼らはそれぞれに証拠を残しました。
最初の証拠は、
一つの目を動かすと、他の目が神に伝わるのです。
二つの clueは、ティベア・ミニール3・4・11でした。
デヴァンは、ヴェルモンに聞きました。
この二つの clueを使っても、
誰も100年以上解決できない人はいないのです。
シャーロック・ホームスは解決できると思うのですか?
ヴェルマンはルーパンだったようで、彼は言った。
今はできるよ。
本の情報が足りなかったんだけど、
教祖は私のために作ったんだ。
一度に帰らなきゃいけないんだ。
ははは、急いでくれ。
ヴェルマンは笑顔で答えた。
はい、シャーロック・ホームズが明日来る前に
貴方の城を盗んでくれ。
All the guests laughed.
Then, Devon said,
Gentlemen, please come back again for a late breakfast tomorrow.
城主ドゥヴァンヌがルパンを恐れて シャーロック・ホームズをイギリスから呼んでいると
うわぁもう早速呼びましたね シャーロック・ホームズ
さてルパンは神父さんのヒントをもとに秘密のトンネルを探し当てれるのか